Brooklyn, NY

blinsay.com blinsay@gmail.com

Interested in distributed systems, infrastructure, and the tools people use to manage them at scale. Works well on a team and independently. Happy on both greenfield and brownfield projects. Experience building and running software in the cloud and on-premise in Rust, Go, Python, and Java.

## **Experience**

#### Engineer, Engineering Manager, Two Sigma Investments (July 2018 - Present)

- Maintained and built critical infrastructure across the Compute and Storage teams. Wrote Kubernetes Operators and clients for storage systems, debugged memory leaks in FUSE, and held a pager for multiple services old enough to vote.
- Managed the team responsible for the scheduling system that powers daily business operations. Turned the team from a keep-the-lights-on skeleton crew into a group capable of delivering impactful new integrations and features like automatic observability and new scheduling modes.

#### Engineer, Bumpers Inc (January 2017 - December 2017)

 Built and ran the backend of a seed-stage social network for amateur podcasters and video creators. Handled CDN configuration, building out search, and everything in between. Used AWS SQS and ffmpeg to build a horizontally scaling rendering pipeline for user-created videos.

# Senior Engineer, Kickstarter PBC (August 2014 - January 2017)

• Replaced a third-party analytics pipeline with AWS Redshift and Looker, saving the company six figures a year. Built tools on top of Redshift that empowered the data team to quickly iterate on data products, like a new recommendation engine.

## Infrastructure Engineer, Aggregate Knowledge Inc (July 2013 - May 2014)

 Maintained streaming data infrastructure that handled tens of thousands of messages a second. Built a batch-processing pipeline in AWS that enabled the company to scale for large customers.

### Engineer, Boundary Inc (October 2012 - July 2013)

• Worked on a team that maintained a distributed streaming system analyzing high-volume networking data. Built and deployed an IPFIX collector that handled 1 Gb/second of ingress traffic.

#### Data Scientist, Aggregate Knowledge Inc (April 2010 - September 2012)

- Worked on research projects and ad-hoc consulting projects that resulted in the acquisition of multiple major clients.
- Designed a novel model for Multi-Touch Attribution (US Patent 9891967).

#### Education

B.S. in Mathematics, 2010 University of Chicago, Chicago IL